管道用具区在通道四
Anybody in plumbing, please go to aisle four.
我的神呐
God damn!
你刚拿着的是得伟充电式吧
Ah, I see you got the DeWalt cordless.
得伟410--钉枪
Your nail gun-- DeWalt 410.
没错 问题是这玩意在车里搁一段时间
Yeah. The trouble is, you leave it in a truck for a while,
当赶着急用时
need to step up and use the bitch,
电池就撑不住了
the battery don't hold up, you know?
是啊 这是充电式的通病
Yeah, cordless'll do that.
你也可以考虑下火药驱动工具
You might want to consider the powder-actuated tool.
例如喜得利DX 460 MX或辛普森PTP--
The Hilti DX 460 MX or the Simpson PTP--
这两款可是我的镇店之宝
these two are my Cadillacs.
不得不说 架子上的其他款式都略逊一筹了
Everything else on this board is second-best, sorry to say.
你是要搞建筑的 还是家用啊?
Are you contracting, or just doing some work around the house?
不 我们工作用
No, we work all over.
长时间的?
Full time?
不 上个月我们大概接了5个活
No, we had about five jobs last month.
这样的话 购买火药驱动钉枪也是物有所值的
Ah. With that rate, the cost of the powder-actuated guns justifies itself.
- 你说"动力"? - 我说火药
- You say "power"? - Powder.
- 枪支火药的火药? - 是的
- Like gunpowder? - Yeah.
DX 460是药膛口径27的全自动式
The DX 460 is fully automatic, with a.27-caliber charge.
不论是木头 水泥 还是钢板--
Wood, concrete, steel to steel--
没有她射不穿的
she'll throw a fastener into anything.
而且在我看来
And for my money, she handles recoil
她的后坐力相比辛普森或是P3500要来得轻
better than the Simpson or the P3500.
你知道后坐力是什么意思吧?
Now, you understand what I mean by recoil?
当然 就是反冲力我懂你的意思
- Yeah, the kickback. I'm with you. - That's right.
- 没错 - 点27口径吗
.27 caliber, huh?
是啊 虽不是大口径弹道 但是用来钉钉子也是绰绰有余
Yeah, not large ballistically, but for driving nails, it's enough.
口径越大 后坐力也就越强
Any more than that, you'd add to the recoil.
操 我看有人拿着个22口径的装圆头弹
Man, shit. I seen a tiny-ass.22 round-nose
射倒了一个黑鬼让他躺了好几天
drop a nigga plenty of days, man.
那帮操蛋的觉得只是玩玩弹珠游戏 往死里整你
Motherfuckers get up in you like a pinball, rip your ass up.
虽说伤筋动骨--
Big joints, though-- big joints, man,
断了好几根骨头 不过也只能在那边骂娘了
just break your bones, you say, "Fuck it."
我就要这个了 老兄 多少钱?
I'm gonna go with this right here, man. How much I owe you?
含税价669块
$669 plus tax.
不 不 不 你在收银台付钱就行
No no, you just pay at the register.
兄弟 你过去帮我搞定后续吧
Nah, man, you go ahead and handle that for me, man.
剩下的给你当费时间介绍的小费
And keep the rest for your time.
- 这里是800块
This is $800.
- 那又怎样? 你一副热络的蠢样不就是为了挣钱嘛
So what, man? You earned that buck like a motherfucker.
收着吧
Keep that shit.
- 搞定了?
We good?
是啊 兄弟
Yeah, man.
卖的人说作为钉枪来说,这算是枪中极品了 兄弟
The man said if you want to shoot nails, this here is the Cadillac, man.
他应该用臻品来形容可惜他不懂这词
He mean Lexus, but he ain't know it.
- 电池持久力比之前的更长吗 - 哥们 滚你丫的充电式
- Hold the charge better? - Man, fuck the charge.
这玩意儿可是火药驱动的 点27口径
This here is gunpowder-activated, .27 caliber,
全自动 无后冲力 扔飞镖伤人 哥们
full auto, no kickback, nail-throwing mayhem, man.
哪比得上这玩意儿带劲
Shit right here is tight.
滚你丫的只能往镖盘上扔镖
Fuck just nailing up boards.
有了这玩意儿我们还可以干掉几个混球
We could kill a couple motherfuckers with this right here.
笑屁啊 我是受你影响 跟你说真的
You laughing. I've been schooled, dog.
- 好吧 好吧 - 我说真的
- I'm trying to tell you. For real. - All right, all right.
火线重案组 第四季 第1集
the.wire.s04e01
* When you walk through the garden *
* you gotta watch your back *
* well I beg your pardon *
* walk the straight and narrow track *
* if you walk with Jesus *
* he's gonna save your soul *
* you gotta keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* he's got the fire and the fury *
* at his command *
* well you don't have to worry *
* if you hold on to Jesus hand *
* we'll all be safe from Satan *
* when the thunder rolls *
* just gotta help me keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* we'll all be safe from Satan *
* you gotta help me keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* keep the devil *
这是羊入虎口了啊 - Marcia Donnelly
Marlo Stanfield BPI# 392.49
7个了 还在不断增加
Seven and counting.
都在我们的监听范围内了
All of them caught on the wire.
我们暂时还没整装出动 但是也是待发状态了
We're not above the corners yet, but we soon will be.
他们难道不经常更换手机吗
They're not dumping phones?
大概一个月换一次
Every month or so.
这个频率足够我们追踪到
Sloppy enough that we may be able to track a phone or two up to Marlo
Marlo或是他亲信的一两个电话了
or the people he keeps close.
事实上 只要他们如今在用手机通话
Truth is, if they're still using cell phones in this day and age,
他们就在我们的掌控之内
they're mine.
要是Marlo Stanfield也在用手机 他照样逃不出我们的五指山
And if Marlo Stanfield is on a cell, he'll be mine too.
好酷的Lester自吹风格
Cool Lester smooth.
这可不是我自吹自擂 亲爱的 这是显而易见的事实
That's not trash talk, darling. That's simple fact.
就算Marlo Stanfield有很多心腹很多地盘
Marlo Stanfield may have a lot of heart and a lot of corners,
一旦他落到我们手里 那他就是狼群里的幼崽了
but he's a babe in the woods when it comes to this right here.
追踪Barksdales这种大鳄不会辱没了我 但是像Stanfield这种小角色
I was proud to be chasing those Barksdales, but this Stanfield kid...
没有我们预计的激烈
Not as fierce as we thought.
几个月下来 没有一宗凶杀案是可以指向他的
For months now, there hasn't been a body we can put to him.
嗯
Hmm.
你们两个好像有点失望啊
You two sound disappointed.
这个部门需要一些强有力的目标 不然就会越发势弱了
This unit needs good, hard targets, or it'll go soft.
话虽如此 我想你肯定还需要再监听个30天吧.
Be that as it may, I'll assume you want another 30 days on your taps.
至少 我们收到传票这星期要出庭
At least. And we've got subpoenas to go out this week as well.
传票?
Subpoenas?
资产调查
Asset investigations.
关于Marlo Stanfield的?
On Marlo Stanfield?
过来
Come here.
这些是Barksdale的所有资金路径
All this is from the Barksdale money trail.
我们正在审查 当初从Stringer的住所
We've been running down all the paper we pulled out of Stringer's apartment
以及市中心B & B办公室拿来的文件
and the B & B office downtown.
我想Prez了
I miss Prez, man.
- 真的 - 我听见了
- I do. - I hear you.
事实上到处都有这些家伙的资金涉入--
The truth is, those guys had money going everywhere--
投资 政治捐款 咨询费...
investments, political donations, consulting fees...
你打算现在追查这些?
You want to do this now?
一年前我就想追查了
I wanted to do this a year ago,
但是新案子接踵而来
but fresh cases got in the way.
你们头对这些文件没什么意见吗
And your lieutenant's gonna okay this kind of paper?
我们头英勇无畏
Our lieutenant has a fearless heart.
- 这些够让你着手调查了 - 哇哦 哇哦 哇哦 等等 等等 等等 给我等下
- This will get you started. - Whoa whoa whoa. Wait wait wait. Wait right there.
我的优惠券
My coupons.
你差点把我的优惠券给她了
You were gonna give this lady my coupons.
我都夹这儿两天了
Been clipping them for two days,
你竟然因为一时粗心差点给送出去
and you damn near sent them out with your mess.
- 谁叫你放在我的文件堆里? - 谁叫你的文件堆在我的办公区?
- Well, why are they in my pile? - Why is your pile in my workspace?
因为我在干实事!
Because I'm doing real work!
我看你唯一干的事就是不停惹毛我
Working my nerves is what you've been doing.
恰逢巴尔的摩市长初选一个月前
Four weeks before the Baltimore City primary,
你就给我整了一堆洗毒品赃款的传票
you hand me a stack of drug-money subpoenas
而且当中均有涉及一帮政治高官
that hit a dozen key political figures.
有竞选吗
There's an election:
谁在竞选?
Who's running?
...他们觉得我没戏
...and they think I can't.
妈的 我可受不了现任那家伙再来个四年
Shit, I don't think we can take four more years of this guy.
这城市已经腐臭不堪
This city's in the toilet.
我在任那会儿他们也是这么说的
That's what they said during my term, too.
因为你本来接手的就是副烂摊子 暴动什么的
Yeah well, you got dealt a bad hand, I mean, with the riots and all.
是啊 没错
Yeah, sure.
不管怎样 要是Tony Gray的选票低于25% 26%  我想我可能还有戏
Anyway, I think I'll squeeze in if Tony Gray draws off 25%, 26% of the vote,
因为大部分票数是从Royce那边过来的
because most of that's out of Royce's base.
Gray能得个25%已经很不错了 不是吗
25% is a big number for Gray, don't you think?
谁知道呢 反对Royce的人增加了
I don't know. Royce's negatives are up--
其中甚至都有黑人选民
even among black voters.
是啊 再等会儿吧 Norman
Yeah. In a minute, Norman.
知道我在想什么吗 Tommy?
You know what I think, Tommy?
不管你想什么 只要在这里脱颖而出
No matter what, you got your name out there,
就会对你以后踏入议会 大有裨益
and it'll help you down the road if you ever want to step up to the legislature.
不过作为你的同胞我不得不承认
But as one paisan to another,
这里白人市长的时代已经终结了
the day of the white mayor is over in this town.
打搅了 阁下
Excuse me, Your Eminence.
你在Baylor-Edison老人中心有一次演讲
You're due at the Baylor-Edison Senior Center,
我可不想因为你整个早上满口不离本行
and I don't want to be lying to a roomful of wrinkle-assed voters
而去欺骗那些大叔大妈选民们
because you wanted to talk shop all the damn morning.
老年人吗 他们也是选民 Tommy
Seniors, huh? They vote, Tommy.
我得赶紧走了 失陪
Got to run. Sorry.
候选人的行程是由你来安排的 别让他忘了这点
The candidate's on your clock. Don't ever let him forget it.
当然不会
No, indeed.
行车记录簿
Need your sig on vehicle logs
矫正过的法庭报告
and a corrected court report
办公室备忘录传召上庭的要求书
and office memo subpoena requests
以及向市政采购部申请购买大吊扇费用的申请书都需要你签字
and a requisition due to City Purchasing for a large fan.
风扇?
A fan, huh?
Caroline抱怨说 监听室门关着太热了
Caroline says it stays hot in the wire room with the door closed.
哦 这真漂亮 中尉
Oh. It's beautiful, Lieutenant.
- 我还没见过这么漂亮的海边小屋呢 - 真的吗
- I've never seen a beach house so fine. - You think so?
靠 竟然都让我萌生退意了
Shit. Makes me think about retirement,
我还有九年就要退休了
and I only got nine years on.
准备什么时候动工?
When do you break ground?
要是拿到许可证了的话 明年三月动工
Next March, if I have my permits,
想起来了...星期二
which reminds me-- on Tuesday,
我还要去Delaware见我的承包商
I have to get over to Delaware and see my contractor.
哦 没问题
Oh, no problem.
那天的工作就交给我和Lester吧
Me and Lester, we'll cover for you on that.
没问题的
No problem at all.
传唤申请
随手搞定
Cake.
你知道我的意思吧 嘿?  我在跟你说我孩子他妈呢 嘿
You know what I'm saying, yo? That's my baby's mother we talking about, yo.
可你们不是早分手了吗
But y'all been broke up, right?
哥们 我已经没跟她怎么纠缠了
Man, I ain't living with her or nothing,
只是不时给她点零钱花花
but I still be giving her a couple dollars here and there,
做做面子功夫
you know, stop and pass.
Pandemic! Pandemic!
看那
Look at this.
嘿 Nay
Hey, Nay.
- Namond! - 嗯?
- Namond! - Hmm.
我他妈花钱是请你来干嘛的 黑鬼?
What the fuck am l paying you for, nigga?
哦 我错了 B
- Oh, my fault, B. - Pandemic!
见鬼!
- Damn! - Pandemic!
嘿 哥们 管管你那小马尾
Yo man, and do something with that ponytail.
你这样能直接把大老远的条子都引过来 要不扎起来要不处理掉!
Cops can make his ass from a mile away. Braid it or something!
你知道 我跟Patrice在一起也有段时间了
Yeah, you know, me and Patrice been together for a long time.
可你不是说她跟那个Fruit跑了吗
Yeah, but you say she running with the boy Fruit now, right?
是啊 要不是丫的闪得快
Yeah. If he don't back the fuck off,
我就找人爆他菊 嘿
I'm gonna fill his ass with some hot ones, yo.
靠 你觉得我在信口开河吗
Shit. You don't think I will?
我有Pandemic卖
I got that pandemic.
哥们...
Man...
看着点
do what you gonna do.
- Bodie - 你好啊 兄弟?
- Bodie. - What's up, big man?
我们都一星期没你消息了 哥们
You ain't real with us all week, man.
你是囤积居奇还是怎么着
You stepping on that package or what
嘿 兄弟 一切进展太慢了
Yo, man, everything's slow.
自我们从Fayette街迁来后 事情就没快过
It been slow since we moved down here from Fayette Street.
是啊 谁叫Marlo要Fayette这块地盘呢
Yeah, well, Marlo wanted Fayette.
哥们 我可不想对黑鬼们让步
Man, I do not like backing down from niggas, man.
整得自己像个小混混 成天无所事事
I feel like a punk. I feel like doing shit.
时光不再了 哥们
Ain't like the old days, dog.
Barksdale市长走了
Mayor Barksdale left.
你是自己做决定出来混的
You out here on your own, dog.
放弃吧
Give it up.
B 我们走吧
B, let's roll.
嘿 Lex 兄弟
Hey, Lex, man,
你想听实话 我就老实跟你讲了
I'm gonna give you the truth because you need the truth.
Marlo这家伙把这圈子弄得乌烟瘴气
That boy Marlo got the world by the ass.
还有Fruit 他是Marlo的手下
And Fruit, he work for Marlo.
所以我想说 别理那婊子了
So I'm saying, fuck that bitch.
向前看吧
Pfft. And move on.
- 形势逼人啊 - 是啊
- That's just the way it is. - Yeah.
- 形势逼人啊 哥们 - Pandemic!
- That's just the way it is, man. - Pandemic!
谢谢你 先生
Thank you, sir.
请稍等一下 夫人
Just one moment, ma'am.
看到Hoskins了吗
You seen Hoskins?
中尉已经上楼去了
Lieutenant went upstairs already.
请往前走
Step through, please.
主席
Madam President.
议会主席可真够辣的
Council president's hot as balls.
能让我上她 就算是让我先上你都行
I'd fuck you to fuck her, man.
你说真的?
Yeah?
为了睡个辣妹 你真能去睡男人?
You'd fuck a guy for a chance to fuck a hot broad?
你不觉得你这样看起来像是同志吗
You don't think that makes you a faggot or nothing?
不过是个表达方式而已 哥们
It's just an expression, man.
你被派来多久了?
Been on this detail how long?
8个月
Eight months.
跟Clarence Royce共处了8个月
Eight months with Clarence Royce.
那我就直问了
So let me ask,
你做好为巴尔的摩市长挡子弹的准备了吗
are you ready to take a bullet for the Mayor of Baltimore?
中尉先生
Lieutenant, sir.
车可以了吗 还是要另叫一辆?
Is the truck okay, or do we want to call one?
不用了 车可以用了
No, the truck works.
他说只要给他10分钟就好
He said he needed just 10 minutes.
不 现在不行
No, not now.
明天吧
Maybe tomorrow.
又是Krawczyk吗
Is that Krawczyk again?
每次他开张支票
Every time he writes another check,
就会转过头来诸多要求  只是为了证明他有多能耐
he turns around and calls for something just to see that he can.
我们也接到了Carcetti智囊团那边的电话
Getting calls from Carcetti's people, too.
他们想要跟我们进行一次关于犯罪与安全
They want one debate for crime and safety,
经济投资与学校教育的辩论
the other on economic stuff and schools,
Tony Gray跟他也是同个腔调
Tony Gray crying the same blues.
貌似他们准备就用犯罪率 来跟我打擂台了
Like they're gonna get the whole night to smack me with the crime rate.
我跟"阳光"报说了  我们乐意接受任意形式的挑衅
I told "The Sun" paper we're open to any format,
就在这几天 我们会表明立场
which we'll be for another couple days or so, in which time we'll say,
"滚你丫的 一次辩论"
"Fuck you. One debate."
两次辩论 靠!
Two debates. Shit!
操蛋的废物Carcetti
That lost-ball-in-high-grass motherfucker Carcetti.
他得尝尝在不毛之地生存的滋味了
He needs to get used to life in the wilderness,
不只是市区范围内
and not just the downtown areas,
同样也包括东部地区你们现在生活的社区
but your communities here on the East Side.
我们是一条绳上的蚂蚱
We stand or we fall together,
今天我在此是为了让大家得到共进的机会
and I'm here today to ask for the chance to stand with you.
谢谢大家抽时间听此次演讲
Thank you for your time.
有什么问题吗
Questions?
请说 夫人?
Yes, ma'am?
今天的午餐是Salisbury牛排
Is it the Salisbury steak for lunch today,
还是墨西哥夹饼?
or is they doing tacos?
因为这是我们目前的发展目标
Because it's developments like this one,
拟建高层住宅楼
planned residential towers
湖边设置商用空间 酒店
with waterside retail space and restaurants
这样可以扩大巴尔的摩市的计税基础 有利于城市的重建
that grow Baltimore's tax base and help rebuild our city.
在此我要感谢Ed Bowers 感谢他的远见
I want to thank Ed Bowers for his vision,
但更多的 是感谢他作出的承诺--
but more important, for his commitment--
感谢他对巴尔的摩市作出的承诺
for his commitment to the City of Baltimore.
Ed
Ed.
市长先生
Mr. Mayor,
在此我要感谢您以及您领导的政府班底
I want to thank you and your administration,
感谢您让下一阶段重新发展
for making this next stage of redevelopment
巴尔的摩港口城市这一计划能得以实现
for Baltimore's harbor a reality.
说到远见以及承诺--
You talk about vision and commitment--
Clarence Royce市长当之无愧
Mayor Clarence Royce.
Pandemic! Pandemic!
你好啊 Nay?
What up, Nay?
嘿 你好啊?
Yo, what up?
- 你看什么呢?
What you got?
没什么  是讲来自北方森林的A.J.的故事
Nothing. It's just a story about A.J. from North & Woods.
嘿 他们竟然给了他700年?
Yo, you know they gave him 700 years?
看看这胡诌乱造的 哥们
Read this shit, son.
这条街连个人影都没有 你还要上工?
This corner is dead, man. You still working?
对啊 我们准备到下条街  去抓几个新的买主
Yeah, because we was gonna gonna go under the road and catch some fresh birds.
我不知道 我去问问看能不能先走 等等
I don't know. Let me see if I can bounce. Hold up.
- 嘿 B - 什么事?
- Hey, B. - What's up?
我想问下我可不可以先闪
I wanted to know if I could leave early because me and the fellas
我跟我朋友想去Mondawmin  买些返校用的东西
want to go down to Mondawmin for some back-to-school stuff.
你买返校用的东西干嘛? 你他妈给我老实呆着
What you need back-to-school stuff for? Your ass stay suspended.
拜托 别玩了 B
Come on, stop playing, B.
嘿 要不是入了社会长教训 估计你丫的还在幼稚园混呢
Hey, if it wasn't for social promotion, your ass would still be in pre-K, motherfucker.
说不定还要别人给你把屎把尿
Probably daycare up this bitch.
这里有Pandemic!
Pandemic right here!
操 嘿 兄弟
Fuck it. Hey, yo, man.
给这迟到早退的家伙五小时的工钱 哟
Pay this late-to-work, early-to-play nigger out for five hours, yo.
哟 你明天还得把时间补给我
Yo, you owe me extra time tomorrow, though.
Lex! 没听到我说话吗
Lex! Did you hear me?
操 没一个省心的!
Damn, y'all!
现在的年轻人一点职业道德都没有
Young'uns don't got a scrap of work ethic nowadays, man.
要不是看在他老爸的面子上 我就直接炒了他了事
If it wasn't for his pops, I wouldn't even bother.
哟!
Yo!
明天给我早点过来  工作可不会一直这么散漫的
Make sure you come early tomorrow because it ain't always gonna be this slow.
Pandemic!
至少我是这么希望的
At least I hope it ain't.
市长先生
Mr. Mayor.
市长先生 打搅了
Mr. Mayor, excuse me.
我想确认下
I just want to make sure we're still okay
关于Boston街的中位切分没什么问题吧
for that median cut on Boston Street.
为了让那地方可行利用 我真的需要您的许可
I really need that access to make the site viable.
是吗 我会让我的人留意下的
Right. I'll get my people on it.
谢谢你 先生
Thank you, sir.
他的中位出什么问题了吗
Something going on with his median?
他付钱了就没事了
Not once he ponies up.
我觉得他出4,000太少了点
I think he can do a lot better than the 4,000,
你不觉得吗
don't you?
我对这个没兴趣
I don't even want to know.
哦 Chris 求你别杀我 求你
No, Chris, please, man.
我们石灰用完了 哥们
We're low on quicklime, man.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
我们两边都有空位 他反正都会发臭的
We got vacants on both sides. He'll stink is all.
Chris 求求你
Chris, please.
别担心 大哥 我会把你处理好的
Don't fret, boss. I got you covered.
干净利落 我保证
Quick and clean, I promise.
Chris--
Chr--
哥们 这种傻缺的办法连卡通里都不用了
Man, shit like that don't even work in them cartoons.
槲鸡在那边抢夺鸟饵和书本
The roadrunner just snatch the birdseed and book.
- 我们可不是在演卡通片 - 不 你有在演
- We ain't in no cartoon. - Yeah, you is.
嘘! 安静
Shh! Be still.
- 就是 你都把鸟儿吓走了 - 我说的是你们两个
- Yeah, you scaring away the birds. - I'm talking to both y'all.
你们拉我翘班就为了这种无聊事?
Took me off the clock for this craziness? What the fuck is you thinking?
- 你他妈脑子没问题吧?我们相当认真 Nay - 这鸟值300或400
We're serious, Nay. This bird could be worth like 300 or 400.
得了吧 鬼佬
Nigga, please.
哟 知道负责照料Marlo鸽笼名叫Nemo的小子吗
Yo, you know the boy Nemo who worked Marlo's pigeon coop?
他说他一只白色家养鸽卖了400
Said he got 400 for a white homing bird.
- 那是家养的吗 - 至少它是白的
- And that's a homer? - I mean, it's white.
- 所以白的就是家养的喽? - 很可能
- So that makes it a homer, right? - It could be.
见鬼!哥们  那你得在陷阱里放点汉堡肉什么的
Damn! Son, you need to put some hamburger meat in that trap.
- 这样那玩意早就是瓮中鳖了 - 你不废话的话我早就得手了
- That shit would've been got. - Shut your mouth, it'd have been got.
妈的那黑鬼真欠抽
I'm gonna fuck this nigga up.
嘿 哟 你他妈脑子有问题啊 乱扔瓶捣乱是吧
Hey yo, what the fuck is wrong with you, throwing bottles and shit, huh?
你刚吓走了我们白花花的银子 知道吗
You just cost us cash money, you know that?
我又没做什么
I ain't done nothing.
你他妈是傻逼吧
You're a seriously backwards dude. You know that, right?
还在那边玩臭虫 像个打尿包的小屁孩一样
Playing with bugs like he's still in Pampers.
有必要这么毒舌吗
That wasn't even necessary.
你是不用打尿包 你是直接把尿包
Nah, you don't want any Pampers. Put them over that mouth you got.
打在你满口喷屎的嘴上了
Catch all that shit you be flushing.
你他妈嘴巴放毒气呢
Y'all be stinking like rat fart.
开打了!
There you go!
- 哦 哦! - 撂倒他!
- Oh oh! - Get him!
好了 好了 住手 住手
All right, all right. Come on, come on, come on. Come on.
- 你们两个搞得像是泼妇骂街 - 你们两个搞得像是泼妇骂街
- Y'all acting like little bitches. - Yo, you seen my man Duke?
瞄准对方的头打
Clocked him, got him upside his head.
我是因为不想离那货太近  沾上什么不干不净的
Only because I didn't want to get too close and touch the dirty motherfucker.
说不定被传染个艾滋或是什么乌七八糟的病
Could have come up with AlDS or some shit like that.
Dukie打架像个娘们 哟
Dukie fight like a bitch, yo.
我要不是可怜他早就把他抽翻了
I would have whipped that ass if I didn't feel sorry for him.
Duke 兄弟 谁叫你把鸟给吓走了
Duke, man, you scared away the birds.
我炸了个杀虫剂 你想看炸后的碎片吗
I blew me up a bug bomb. You want to come and see the pieces?
不 算了 我要走了
Nah, I'm good. I got to go.
好吧
All right.
嘿 嘿 Randy
Hey hey, Randy.
那鸽子不是家养的
That pigeon wasn't a homer.
家养鸽的脚上都拴着铁环之类的
Homers got them metal things around their leg.
下次你可以教他们怎么分辨
That way you can tell them from the other birds.
你怎么知道的?
How you know that?
Nemo有时会让我打扫他的鸽笼
You know Nemo let me clean out his coop sometimes.
所以...他教过我
So... he was schooling me.
...我们现在一共还剩下54个
...which leaves us a total of 54.
谁会回来已经毫无悬念了-- 还是跟往常一样
No surprises on who's coming back-- all the regulars.
Parker先生和Bowles女士离职了
We lost Mr. Parker and Ms. Bowles.
- Gregory辞职了? - 他跳槽到郡里了
- Gregory's leaving? - Hired by the county.
还有Bowles 我早知道她不会回来了
And Bowles, I knew she wasn't coming back,
当时她班级被毁得一塌涂地
the way they tore up her classroom.
所以我们还缺两个数学老师 4个科学老师
So we're short two in math and four in science.
有人到访 没有系统身份辨识卡 不过他说他是第一次来
Man at the door. No system l.D., but says he's new here.
在他变卦前 放他进来
Well, buzz him in before something changes his mind.
从左边往前走
All the way on the left.
使劲拉
Pull it hard.
使劲!
Hard!
- 锁住了 - 算了 我马上下来
- It's locked. - All right. I'll be right down.
这里他妈的啥都不灵
Not a goddamn thing up in here works like it should.
你翻到餐厅安排那一页
Well, you turn to the cafeteria assignments,
瞧瞧 第二节课 就只有Ernest了
and you see that's gonna leave Ernest alone for second period,
他一个人可干不了
and he can't handle it alone.
你自我介绍吧 名字太拗口了我不想说
You tell them, because I ain't even gonna try to pronounce it.
我是Roland Pryzbylewski
Roland Pryzbylewski.
大家都叫我"Prez"
Everyone just calls me "Prez."
我是Claudell Withers 学校的校长
Claudell Withers. I'm principal here.
你在数学教授上是新手
New in math.
明年我才能拿到教师证
I won't have my certificate until next year,
根据住校教师课程 他们说由于教师短缺
but with the resident teachers' program, they said I'd be getting classes
- 我能开始任教? - 天哪 真是待宰的羔羊
- because of staff shortages? - Jesus. Lambs to the slaughter here.
在你决定从教之前你是做什么工作的 Pryzbylewski先生?
What did you do before you decided to teach, Mr. Pryzbylewski?
我是市里的...警察
I was a police... in the city.
我是Marcia Donnelly 校长助理
Marcia Donnelly, Assistant Principal.
欢迎来到Edward Tilghman中学
Welcome to Edward Tilghman Middle.
从这12次巡视来看只能由Tullman来了
That leaves Tullman, as I see 'em, for the 12th.
- 你觉得他能应付整个轮班吗 - 对了 到底哪个是Tullman?
- You think he can handle the whole shift? - Now, which one's Tullman, again?
红发菜鸟 长得有点像回到梅伯里的Opie
Goofy redhead, kind of looks like Opie from Mayberry,
除了凶猛程度略逊一筹
but less fierce.
Jimmy 少校要见你
Jimmy, Major wants to see you.
Jimmy 进来
Jimmy, come on in.
我知道我刚来这里的时候就已经跟你提过了
I know I offered when I first came over here,
我也知道你当时给我的答复 但是我还是要问问你
and I know your answer then, but I'm still asking.
我想把你调出巡警部
Can I get you out of a radio car?
谢谢 不用了 少校
No thank you, Major.
McNulty 我制定的运行组还差两名人手
McNulty, I'm short two men in Ops,
我的增补小队成立的理由不足
and my follow-up squad couldn't make a case to save its life.
让你接警出动 太大材小用了
You're too damn good to be humping calls.
不了 但还是谢谢您的提拔
Thanks for the offer, though.
你以为我没有打着官腔问过他吗
You don't think I asked him 10 times when I was acting commander?
他他妈的真是来错了地方
He's in the wrong fucking place.
对我们来说 确实如此
For us, yeah.
而对他来说...
For him...
哟 条子来了 哥们 条子来了 停工
Yo, po-po, man. Po-po. Shut it down.
你的礼貌呢 Bodie?
Where is the love, Bodie?
你他妈的该有的礼貌呢?
Where is the motherfucking love?
我跟这小孩子渊源深厚 在他青少年时期我就开始追捕他了
I go back so far with this kid, I was chasing him through juvie.
可我们都在这儿了 那些还要紧吗
But does any of that matter when we roll up here?
有人向我招手 点头或微笑了吗
I get so much as a wave, a nod, a smile?
什么都没有
Nothing.
哪怕是问个好啊
How about just hello?
- 你好 - 瞧见了? 这也不难嘛
- Hello. - See? That wasn't so hard, was it?
Lex 伙计 你还好吧
Lex, my man, how's your day going?
不是我说你 你扫漏了一处地方
Not to criticize or anything, but I think you missed a spot there.
小Kevin 过得怎么样啊
Little Kevin, how's it hanging?
Reesey 你怎么哭丧着个脸哪
Reesey, you look like someone just shot your dog.
没事吧 伙计 你还好吧
You all right, man? You okay?
- Reesey算数还是那么糟吗 - 你听到他说的话了吧
- Reesey still messing up the count? - You hear what he said?
唷 老狗 你下月把他送到Lamelle上学去
Yo, dog, you send him up to Lamelle next month.
我让Davis女士帮他补补数学
I'll make sure Ms. Davis puts him in remedial math,
咱今天在这儿就算做好事了
and we'll have done some good here today.
该死的警察来了
Fucking cop, man.
- 没事吧 - 嗯 就说说话
- Everything good? - Yeah. Just words.
诱捕先生 你好吗
Mr. Entrapment, how you doing?
别这样 你那瞎话我还没忘呢
Don't look like that. I'm still dining out on that story.
你知道一年前他怎么让窃听组栽跟头吧
You know how he beat the wiretap a year ago?
在Bunny Colvin设的毒品自由区干活 还说我们是诱捕
Claimed entrapment when he was clocking in Bunny Colvin's Hamsterdam.
见你的鬼
Shit you not.
机灵小子 我喜欢
Smart kiddo. I loved it.
我一小时后转回来  这地方得给我清干净了
When I roll back in an hour, this corner's bone-dry.
你们今天就到这儿为止
Your people are done for the day.
好吧 咱再试试
Okay. So let's try this again.
我说"晚安 Broadus先生"
I say, "Have a good evening, Mr. Broadus."
你也晚安 Carver警官
And a good evening to you, Sergeant Carver.
瞧见了 这不就对了嘛
See? We're right here.
你也晚安 Colicchio警官
And a very good evening to you, Officer Colicchio.
弄把点四零 自己了断去 混账东西
Fuck yourself with a 40, shitbreath.
究竟是怎么事
What the fuck was all that about?
- 你总不能把每个人都爆头吧 Tony - 不能吗
- You can't bust every head, Tony. - I can't?
都爆掉了 发生这种破事 你找谁谈去
Bust every head, who are you gonna talk to when the shit happens?
嗨 Rachel
Hi, Rachel.
- Tim 谢谢你昨天帮忙 - 嗯 不客气
- Tim, thanks for doing that yesterday. - Yeah, no problem.
你整个早上都在迟到
You ran late all morning--
与长者见面迟到 跟Della里程碑式的会面也迟了
Late for the seniors, late for the Stonewall meeting with Della.
与同性恋联盟的会面也迟到了
Late for the Gay-Lesbian Alliance.
那些老家伙嘛 说话慢吞吞
Them seniors, they talk slow.
胡说 是因为跟小Tony早餐才晚了的
Bullshit. It was breakfast with Young Tony
他们坐在那儿 喝着冷咖啡说长道短的
when they sat there swapping stories over cold coffee.
- 小Tony 啊? - 我采纳了明智的建议
- Young Tony, huh? - I was getting sage advice--
- 来自一个只任了一届的市长吗 - 67年接任市长
- From a one-term mayor? - It wasn't his fault.
当时这城市水深火热 不是他的错
He takes over in '67, sees the city burn.
当时那是机会
That was an opportunity.
Spiro Agnew是靠68年的暴乱起的家
Spiro Agnew made his whole career on the '68 Riots.
Agnew?
萝卜青菜 各有所爱
One man's shithead's another man's vice president.
- 今天也同样适用 - 嗨 那是民调数据吗
- True today as it ever was. - Hey, is that polling data?
初步数据 还不完整
Raw numbers. It's incomplete.
现在你该进电话间去 拨键要钱了
Right now, you need to be in the call room dialing for dollars.
嗷 操
Aw, fuck!
我再也做不来了
I can't do it anymore!
我讨厌死这个了 最讨厌就是这个
I hate it. I hate it more than anything.
- 我他妈的恨死它 - 少来了
- I fucking hate it! - You don't do this,
你没钱付过去两周的电视广告费
you don't have the money to pay for the damn TV spots in the last two weeks.
他妈的混蛋
Aw, mothersucking cockfuckers.
天哪 我恨死这事了
Oh, Jesus. I fucking hate this.
嗨 听着 Jim
Hey there, Jim.
我是Tom Carcetti 记得我吗
Tom Carcetti here, remember me?
我们在你姐姐家见过
We met at your sister's house--
就是那个娶了个共和党傻逼的那个
you know, the one that's married to that Republican cunt.
我知道你不记得我了
I know you don't remember me.
我知道你对他娘的政治家没点用处
I know you don't have any use for fucking politicians,
坦白说 你怎么想的 你关注什么
and frankly, I don't give a flying fuck about what you think
我才不管呢
or what your concerns are.
但我关心的是 你那可爱的金发娇妻
But I do care about what your cute little blonde wife
对很多事情的看法
thinks about so many things.
Jim 我来电是因为
But, Jim, the reason I'm calling is because
我想要你给我开张四千块的支票
I want you to write me out a check for $4,000,
法律许可的最大值
the maximum allowed by law.
因为我们不相信你会把支票寄过来
Because we don't trust you to actually mail that check,
我们要派几个临时雇用的 公共工程部工人过去
we're gonna send over a couple of furloughed DPW workers
把你揍一顿 管你要支票
to beat the check out of you.
都说完了? 你需要的是三万块
All finished? You need $30,000...
三小时后要 别扯淡了 Tommy
in the next three hours. No bullshit, Tommy.
打电话吧 要不就死在这里算了
You hit your number or die in this room.
嗯 怎么着都行
Yeah, whatever.
你在看什么呢
So what are you watching, then?
电视上有什么好看的吗
Anything on the tube?
不可能啊
No fucking way.
他们的阵容很棒了
They got enough power in the middle of the lineup.
需要的只是投球而已
What they need is pitching.
你看什么呢
What you looking at?
疯了
Fucking crazy.
以为我真会开车送那混蛋去Woodlawn似的
Oh, like I'm really gonna give that motherfucker a ride to Woodlawn.
该死
Shit.
救命啊 救命
Help! Somebody help!
还好吗 Patrice?
What's up, Patrice?
你就让它这么响着吗
You're letting it ring, right?
响一两声你不会挂掉吗
You're not hanging up after a ring or two?
我在打电话 Terri
I'm making the calls, Terri.
我不知道怎么说 没人在家
I don't know what to say. Nobody's home.
三万块 Tommy
30,000, Tommy.
你是说Lex吗 那个以前跟Patrice拍拖的?
You mean Lex, the boy who used to go with Patrice?
Lester
Lester!
他可是她孩子的爹
He her baby's daddy.
- 他也不是第一个没了命的 - 你不能这么说
- He ain't the first one to get his spurt. - You ain't got to talk like that.
黑鬼在Paragon外头 就这么上前把他了结了
Nigga just walked up to him outside of the Paragon and served him up.
脸部一枪 嘭
- One to the face. - Whap!
哇塞 他真厉害
Shoot. He was real cute.
Lex用他的九毫米干掉了 那个睡眼惺忪的家伙
Lex and his nine took all the cute out of that lazy-eye motherfucker.
Fruit电话有什么收获吗
Anything on Fruit's phone?
没有 我听了两小时了
Nothing. I've gone for two hours.
嗯 嗯
- Sure. - It's no problem, though.
真的 我需要你帮忙
Sure. I really need your help.
- 给我四千 - 行
- Put me down for four. - Yeah.
你太太呢 她能筹到四千吗
What about your wife? Think she can come up with four?
- 八千是不行的 - 小孩呢
- I don't think we can do eight. - The kids?
他们还正蹒跚学步呢
They're in strollers.
我知道 开个玩笑
I know they're in strollers. I was kidding.
好笑
That's funny.
行的 四千很好了 谢谢
Yeah, never mind. 4,000 is good. Thanks.
好说
No problem.
左边太阳穴一枪
One to the left temple.
在人头挤挤的俱乐部停车场 近距离开枪 当然又是没目击者
Close range in a lot full of club trash, but of course, nobody sees a thing.
嗯
Hmm.
- 听说你的枪手叫"Lex" - Lex?
- We hear your shooter goes by "Lex." - Lex?
我们也监听了你们死者的电话
We were up on your victim's cell phone, too.
我们会回放通话 把记录都给你们
We'll go back through the calls, send you whatever's there.
这是在他口袋里找到的
Got this from his pocket.
可以从那儿提取号码 作为安慰奖
You can pull the numbers from that as a consolation prize.
失去一个监听对象 这对你们很打击吧
This fucks you guys up, don't it? Losing a guy you had wired?
不 街头混混的电话 我们监听了好几个
Nah. We're up on several phones on the street level.
有没有Fruit先生 我们照样行
With or without Mr. Fruit, we're on our way.
也真是怪
You know, it's strange.
没怎么死人
We're not seeing bodies.
这可是几个月来第一次毒贩火拼
This is the first drug hit in months,
完蛋的却是Marlo的手下
and it's Marlo's boy who falls.
- 我还以为Marlo是新的毒枭呢 - 他正是
- I thought Marlo was the new power. - He is.
该死的 他名下拥有 从MLK到Fulton等众多房产
Shit, he's got everything from MLK to Fulton now.
不死几个人 他怎么能拥有那么多不动产
How do you hold that much real estate without making bodies?
要是监听到更多有关谋杀的线索 Lester
You hear anything more about this murder on your wire, Lester,
希望你给Bunk打电话
the Bunk expects a call.
嗯 我知道
Yeah, I know he does.
哦 去Norris的
Oh! The hell with Norris.
你才是我真正的搭档 Lester 一辈子的搭档
You're my real partner, Lester. My life partner.
少来这套 贱人
Don't tease, bitch.
看见那瘸腿瘪三吗
Look at that bowlegged motherfucker.
是我让他成这样的
I made him walk like that.
他妈的谁是Lex?
So who the fuck is Lex?
Dontrelle的表弟 以前跟Cantel的人一起混的
Dontrelle's cousin. Used to be with Cantel's people.
他现在负责Hilltop那边的几个点
He working some corner over the Hilltop now.
没有更深的瓜葛了吧
He ain't more connected than that?
他还惹上我的人了?
And he coming near one of mine?
跟生意无关
Wasn't about no business.
是娘儿们的事 伙计
Pussy, man.
唷 Fruit夺走了Lex觉得本属于自己的东西
Yo, Fruit was into something that Lex thought was his own.
你说句话 我们就把那街角给端了
You say the word, we take off that whole motherfucking corner
一个不留
every last one of them bitches.
我们说的是哪个街角啊
What corner are we talking about, again?
Pacer那边的几个烂仔
Rag-tag shit up on Pacer.
伙计 他们的货是管Joe拿的 但他们都是单干的
Man, they get their shit from Joe, but they're mostly independent.
他们死定了 Marlo 说句话吧
They gone, Marlo. Just say so.
你怎么想 把他们都端了?
That what you think? Just do them all?
把他们的地盘也接管了
And take their fucking corner, too.
我要个偏僻的Hilltop街角来干嘛
What do I want with some off-brand Hilltop corner?
没人向我们宣战 我干嘛要杀人呢
And why I need to be stacking bodies when there ain't no one trying to war with us?
就Lex行了
Just Lex.
他干掉了我们的人 他就得死
He did one of ours, so he got to fall.
出去 Tommy 你到了
Get out, Tommy. You're done.
起来 Tommy
Get up, Tommy!
快 靓仔 快
Come on, pretty boy. Come on.
你不必回家 但你不能呆在这儿
You don't have to go home, but you can't stay here.
- 来吧 走啊 - 到家了?
- Come on. Let's go. - That's home?
对 没错
Yeah. That's it.
到了 小骑兵
There we go, little trooper.
明早六点半
6:30 tomorrow morning.
别让我像昨天那天 把你拖下床
Don't make me drag you out of bed like you did yesterday.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
该死 伙计 出什么事了
Damn, boy, what happened to you?
Terrace的手下见我走过 Ramsey街的地盘就打我
Terrace Boys banged me coming across the tracks over there by Ramsey Street.
Teron  Manny  Herbie
Teron, Manny, Herbie.
都是Terrace的爪牙
Man, all them Terrace niggas.
不能让他们这么打Dukie
They can't whoop on Dukie like that.
我知道 只有我们才能这么打Dukie
Yeah, I know. Only we can whoop on Dukie like that.
咱要过去 把这事扯平
We've got to step it up, even this out.
不 不能扯平
Nah. Fuck even.
得让他们遭两倍的罪
We gonna hurt them twice as bad.
揍得他们一辈子忘不了
Give 'em a whoop-ass they ain't gonna never forget.
要是我们直接过去跟他们干 他们的人可是跟我们一样多啊
If we straight-up fight them, there's as many of them as there is us--
更多呢
more even.
- 你什么意思? 怕了? - 不 我是说
- So what you saying? You scared? - Nah, I'm just saying.
给他们颜色瞧瞧 要从长计议
If we're gonna hurt them, we need to think on it.
别就这么揍来揍去的
Do something go past beating on each other.
你是说用枪吧
You talking guns and shit.
不 我不是说枪
Nah, I ain't talking guns.
怎么
What?
啊 好嘛
Aw, shit.
Randy有法子了
Randy got an idea.
嗨 Norman
Hey, Norman.
你知道我昨晚晚餐吃啥
You know what I had for dinner last night?
三文鱼三明治啊 在车上吃的
Tuna sub. I ate in the car.
等我写传记的时候 这事我肯定给写上
When I'm finished writing my memoirs, that shit'll be in there, no doubt.
你知道我刚吃了啥吗 在车上吃的?
You see what I just ate? In the car?
他妈的三文鱼三明治哎
A fucking tuna sub.
为了不让他们发狂 Norman 候选人的菜谱应该有所变化
In order to prevent distemper, Norman, you must vary the candidate's menu.
你要是嚼完了  就听听这些个新的广播宣传带吧
If you're done chewing, Iet's give these new radio spots a listen.
我们已经看到了Tommy Carcetti 当市议会议员能有多大作为了
We've seen what Tommy Carcetti can do at City Hall as a councilman.
当前的管理让位于特殊的利益
While the current administration bent to special interests,
- Tommy Carcetti支持立法... - 什么事
- Tommy Carcetti sponsored legislation... - What?
通过阻止码头区域的过度开发
...that is protecting jobs at the fort
来保护那里的就业机会
by preventing the overdevelopment of our waterfront.
三十万
300,000.
太棒了 多谢
Great. Thanks for sharing.
这就阻碍了重要城市服务的预算削减
...that prevented budget cuts to vital city services...
三后面五个零 市长最新的电视广告费  离竞选只有四周了
Three and five zeroes-- mayor's latest TV buy, and it's four weeks out.
- 把那东西关了 - 你不喜欢这宣传带?
- Turn that shit off! - You don't like the spots?
他们录制前我看过稿子  我觉得挺有力的
I read the copy before the studio mix. I think they're strong.
都是胡说 不堪一击的胡说
They're bullshit! Weak bullshit!
我都不会投票选我自己
I wouldn't vote for me.
操蛋
Fuck!
操蛋Royce 操蛋Tony Gray 我自己也操蛋
Fuck Royce! Fuck Tony Gray! Fuck me!
再说说我这是去哪儿
Where am I going again?
Oliver和中东人聚居区之间的一个社区
One of those neighborhoods between Oliver and Middle East.
中东 好名字嘛 操蛋费卢杰 (伊拉克地名)
Middle East. Now, that's a good name for it-- fucking Fallujah.
御前演出 Victorina Simmons女士
Command performance. Ms. Victorina Simmons.
她对两个大选区有着影响力
She holds sway over two big vote precincts,
不管EDC支持谁都一样--
no matter who the EDC is lying down with--
操蛋Royce 花三十万眼都不眨
Fucking Royce! 300,000 like it's fucking water.
还有Garnett牧师
Then there's also the Reverend Garnett.
他们今天抱怨什么来着
What are they complaining about today?
该死的混蛋们 牢骚满肚的东西
Fucking shithole of a city. Whining bastards,
抱怨垃圾啊 犯罪啊 这个那个的
bitching about the trash or the crime or this or that.
境况这么糟 是我的错
It's my fucking fault it went to shit.
- 这些该死的 - 老大
- These motherfuckers. - Boss.
他们能让我雪上加霜
They can bite my bloody ass.
Simmons女士
Ms. Simmons.
Garnett牧师 很高兴又见到你们
Reverend Garnett. Good to see you again.
我正开着会呢
I had a meeting going on,
但我来了 我知道得来看看
but I'm here now, and I know there's things to see.
我们打了好多电话到市中心 但事情一直没解决
We called and called downtown, and ain't nothing gets done.
- 好的 带路吧 - 这边走 议员
- Okay. Show me. - Right this way, Councilman.
我想让你看的第一个...
The first thing I want you to take a look at...
你都喝了很多了
See, you've got to drink a lot.
想想水是怎么流的吧
Think about the water running.
这样你们就会知道...
And that way, you know--
你怎么知道水是怎么流的 Duke?
How the fuck you know what water running be like, Duke?
去年你家就断水了
Water been off in your house since last year.
- 伙计 冷的 - 对啊 是冷的
- Man, that's cold. - Yeah, that's cold, Nay.
哦 我准备好了
Oh, shit. I'm ready.
黑鬼看着 我尿不出
Can't go with niggers watching, yo.
见鬼
damn.
我们打电话过去
When we call,
多数时候 他会派人来
he'll send somebody, most of the time,
他们会记下来 就像他这样
and they write it all down just like he doing now.
但无济于事
But nothing ever gets done.
到这儿来 议员 你看看这个
Come here, Councilman, I want you to see this.
看到那些嗑药的孩子了?
Now, see them drug boys?
他们像这样堵住巷子 这样警察就追不上他们了
They block the alleys like this so the police won't chase them down there.
- 这些垃圾 - 嗯
- All this trash. - Mm-hmm.
到处是老鼠 屋子都空了
Rats everywhere. Houses vacant.
我们一直要他们过来清理
We keep trying to get them down here and clean this up.
这样不过分吧
I guess that's too much like right.
呃
Well,
事实上 Royce不让任何市政机构 接我的电话 虽然那是受宪法保护的
truth is, Royce won't let the city agencies take any of my constituent calls.
但我来看看怎么解决
But let me see what I can do.
来吧 你来看看这个 来
Come on, let me show you this down here. Come on.
唷
Yo.
你们这些Terrace黑狗腿们 认识一个叫"Deez"的吗?
Y'all Terrace niggas know that boy who go by the name "Deez"?
- Deez? (与"这些"同音) - 对 这些笨蛋
- Deez? - Yeah, Deez nuts.
啊 该死
Aw, fuck.
见鬼
Shit.
唷 唷 快 快 快
Yo yo, come on, come on, come on.
快 抓住他
Yeah, come on, get him!
该死 我就知道那些婊子要伏击我们
Damn! I knew those bitches was gonna set us up.
- 没错啊 婊子们 - 什么意思
- Yeah, fucking say it, bitches. - ???
对Terrace可不能不敬
Don't ever disrespect Terrace.
- 该死 - 我往自己身上泼尿了
- Damn! - I fucking pissed myself.
操蛋
Fuck!
这边
Over here!
从后头踢他
Kick him right behind.
Randy
Randy!
这边来
This way.
嗨 唷 他进了那边
Hey yo, he went in there!
记住与学生沟通时
Remember that phrasing is a cornerstone
措辞是基础
in communicating with your students.
不仅是你所问的问题
This applies not only to the questions you ask
或是他们对课文的理解
or their comprehension of the lesson,
还关乎他们把你看成是什么样的教育者
but how they perceive you as an educator.
那要从哪儿开始呢
And where does that begin?
大声点 热情点
Out loud and enthusiastically.
I.A.L.A.C.
来吧 再来一次
Let's go. Once again.
I.A.L.A.C.
我们要对自己怎么说
And what are we telling ourselves?
我有爱心 有能力
I am lovable and capable.
我看到了那些笑脸
Now I see those smiling faces.
这一页下边的列表
...where the listing on the lower half of the page
标注的是典型的容易受袭的地点
indicates some typical soft-target locations.
对恐怖袭击警觉的警官必须自问
An officer alert to the terrorist threat must ask himself,
"我是否了解自己易受攻击的地点呢?
"Do I know the location of my soft targets,
"那些很多市民聚集的地点"
"those where large numbers of civilians congregate?"
火车站 办公楼 体育馆
--Train terminals, office buildings, stadiums.
教室里热门的地点是削笔刀区域
Another hot zone in the classroom is the pencil sharpener,
小孩喜欢在那儿聚集
where children tend to congregate and--
我的班上曾经有削笔刀
I had a pencil sharpener in my class once.
Antoine Granderson从墙上扯下它 冲我砸了过来
Antoine Granderson ripped it from the wall and threw it at me.
我想知道你的备课本里是否说了
I'd like to know what your lesson plan suggests
什么时候Harold Hounchell会用一套课本 砸开关闭着的窗户
when Harold Hounchell sends a full set of textbooks through a closed window.
谢谢
Thank you.
注意...
attention, attention...
安静 各位
Settle down, everybody.
受生化袭击时的
And for emergency procedures
紧急程序
in the event of biochemical agents,
可以查看附录B
you can refer to Appendix B.
不是看不上你的附录
No disrespect to your appendix,
要是恐怖分子真袭击西方世界
but if them terrorists do fuck up the Western,
难道有谁能预见吗
could anybody even tell?
几个基地分子来到巴尔的摩街上 计划炸掉炸鸡店
Some Al-Qaedas were up on Baltimore Street planning on blowing up the chicken joint.
但Apex的人阻住他们 夺走了他们的骆驼和长袍
But Apex's crew jacked them up, took their camels and robes,
在Leakin公园狠揍他们一顿 至少我听说是这样
buried their ass in Leakin Park. At least that's what I heard.
嗨 要见真的恐怖分子吗 去Pency和Gold吧
Hey, y'all want some real terrorists? You go up on Pencey and Gold.
嗨 伙计们 继续开...
Hey, guys, let's maintain our--
你干得不赖嘛
You're doing one heck of a job.
一个字也别再说了
Not another fucking word.
谢谢
Thank you.
那么...
So...
嗯
Mmm.
你这禽兽
You beast.
我就是忍不住 你让我心旌摇动
I can't help it. You stirred my manhood.
小蓝孩
Little Boy Blue.
你他妈来这干吗
What the fuck are you doing here?
我有个案子
I caught one.
一个叫Lex的街头毒贩
Got a street dealer who goes by the name of Lex.
Lester窃听到的
Lester heard it on the wire.
Lester在搞窃听?
Lester's up on the wire:
该死的 你消息真闭塞
Shit, boy, you are out of the loop.
认识这家伙吗 叫Lex的?
You know this mutt? Goes by Lex?
很眼熟
He is familiar.
你知道该问谁吗 Carver
You know who you should ask? Carver.
- 呃... - 他会喜欢这活的
- Naw... - He'd love the job, man.
好吧 就找Carver
All right. Carver it is.
- 我还是觉得该拉下你的衣服 - 干吗
- I still feel the need to pull your coat. - For what?
体验一下 Jimmy 领略一下
The taste, Jimmy. The taste.
咱俩去咱喜欢的地方转转如何
How about you and me hit a few of our favorite spots?
我去和威士忌 你去听Jamey的歌
You know, me on the Glenlivet, you on the Jamey?
看看是否还是昔日的样子
Go see if that train is still on the track.
找个晚上过来吃晚饭如何
Why don't you come round some night for dinner?
见见Beadie和孩子们
Say hey to Beadie and the ankle-biters.
晚饭?
Dinner:
...位于高楼之中
...Iocated in high-rise structures,
还要沿途细查住宅
as well as residences are detailed alongside...
谢谢 Santy
Thanks, Santy.
这种胡言也买账? 不是吧
This horseshit? You serious?
拿回学校给孩子们用
Back to school for the kids.
嗨 唷 Namond 我会还你钱的
Hey. Yo, Namond, I'll pay you back.
没你的钱
You ain't never gonna have no money.
唷 Michael 被他们打了?
Yo, Michael, they got you?
没什么 混战而已
Ain't nothing but a scuffle, man.
不过大伙儿都回来了 对吧
Everybody made it back, though, right?
不 他得去缝几针
Naw, man, he had to the boss to get some stitches.
- 被砖头砸了 - 你衣服都换了
- He got hit with a brick. - I see you changed clothes already.
不得已呗 他当时臭死了
He had to. Yo, he was stinking.
唷 Randy 都是你的馊主意
Yo, Randy, man, that was the stupidest thing you ever thought of.
但还是挺有意思的 没错吧
But it was kind of funny when it happened, though. You know what I'm saying?
他走前 你要什么吗
Yo, you want something before he bounce?
我来给钱
I'm buying.
- 每个英勇战斗的人都有份 - 我也参加了
- One for every soldier that stood tall. - I was down there.
去你妈的 Duke
Yeah, fuck you, Duke.
你全身而退?
So you get out all right?
嗯 跑过街角的时候扭到脚踝了 不过...
Yeah. Hurt my ankle going around the corner, but--
不过你逃了 对吧
But you got away, then?
副州长气急败坏
The lieutenant governor is up in arms
因为两个民主党国家委员会...
because two Democratic National Committees...
- 我知道我们迟了 - 没什么 你干得不错
- I know we're way late-- - Ain't no thing. You did good here.
把那烂玩意儿关了
Turn that bullshit off.
你真以为他们会投票选一个白人?
You really think they're gonna vote for the white guy?
很长时间来 黑人都投票选白人啊
Black folk been voting white for a long time.
你说得对 我们就听
You come correct, we listen.
是你们不肯投票选黑人罢了
It's y'all that don't ever vote black.
见鬼 不过我是会选你的
Shit, you got my vote, anyway.
你不会选我吗 Norman
I don't have your vote, Norman?
你是我的竞选经理 却不选我?
You're my deputy campaign manager, and I don't have your vote?
白人中我只会选Bobby Kennedy
Last white man I could vote for was Bobby Kennedy,
你又不是他
and you ain't no Bobby K.
你刚才不是说...
I thought you just said--
我是泛指黑人和善的天性
I was speaking in general about the kindly nature of black folks.
而我比较特别 没那么和善
In particular, I ain't all that kindly.
这么说 你他妈的拿我的钱
So you're gonna take my fucking check
帮我竞选
and run with my fucking campaign--
我知道谁是我东家  是 先生 噢 是的 老板
Well, I do know who pays me. Yes, sir! Oh yes, sir, boss!
你要投给谁 Royce? Tony Gray?
Who are you gonna vote for? Royce? Tony Gray?
那哥俩中的一个
One of them brothers.
行 行 行
Yeah yeah yeah.
不用我再重复了吧 九点正就得回来
Don't make me tell you again. It's 9:00 sharp, boy.
我闻到了尿味
And I'm smelling what has to be urine.
你干什么去了
What you been at, boy?
我们今天跟Dukie玩来着
Well, we were playing with Dukie today.
你知道他那身衣服什么的都很臭
You know how he be with his clothes and all.
那孩子能有朋友是好事
Well, it's good that child has friends, I suppose.
- 是的 太太 - 进去吧
- Yes, ma'am. - Get in there.
拜托 让我歇歇气吧
Come on, now, give me a break--
拜托 Dougie 我知道很晚了 但我得这么走后门
Come on, Dougie. I know it's late, but I got to come backdoor like this,
否则那些机关屁事不做 你跟我一样清楚
or the agencies won't do shit. You know that as well as I do.
- 拜托 Tommy... - 拜托 Tommy  快点
- Come on, Tommy... - Come on, Tommy. Hustle.
真荒唐 拜托 饶了我吧
This is ridiculous. Come on, give me a break--
听着 Dougie 嗯
Look, Dougie. Yeah.
抱歉往家里打扰你 但那个混蛋Royce
I'm sorry to bug you at home, but this asshole Royce
出了办公室 就不肯出理事情 我需要清理几个巷道
won't handle a thing out of my office, and I need a couple of alleys cleaned.
对 联邦大街1200街区 两侧都要
Yeah. 1200 block of Federal Street, both sides;
还有街两头的Chester和Collington
and then Chester and Collington run in either direction off that.
- 天 Tommy - 我知道你几天后又会当权了
- Jesus, Tommy. - I know, you're gonna be out there again in a couple days.
你能给特别服务处的Frankie打电话 让他派一辆维修卡车
Can you call Frankie in Special Services and have him send a cold patch truck?
联邦大街可是坦克去了都会栽
Federal street's a fucking tank trap.
- 行 行 - 好极了 谢谢 问候Denise
- Yeah yeah yeah. - Great. Thanks. Love to Denise.
快点 Tom
Hustle up, Tom.
你好吗 晚上好啊
How you doing? Good evening.
嗨
Hi.
你都迟到两个多小时了 Tommy
You're over two hours late, Tommy.
不尊重你选区 你是不可能赢的
You ain't gonna win disrespecting your base.
等等 Tony
Hold up, Tony.
听着 我们得谈谈
Look, man. We got to talk.
现在的情形让我很难过
I feel the bad about the way things have turned out,
但不管对错 如果你赢了
but right or wrong, if you're elected,
我会尽力帮你
then I'm gonna do whatever I can to help you,
如果是我赢了 我需要你的帮助
and if I get in, I'm gonna need your help.
这无关私人恩怨 Tony
I mean, it's not personal, Tony.
滚你的蛋 Tommy
Fuck you, Tommy.
这是我的地盘了
So this is me?
是的
This is you.
Pandemic
Pandemic!
Pandemic 这儿有Pandemic哦
Pandemic! Got that pandemic right here!
- 你好吗 - 你好
- What's up? - What's up, man?
我这是今天低价向韩国人买的
I got all this from the Koreans today at a discount.
开学后 我可以三倍价卖出去
When school start, I'll be selling it for three times that.
告诉你吧
Tell you what,
- 给我些糖豆 - Pandemic 这儿有Pandemic
- Iet me get them Skittles. - Pandemic! pandemic right here!
不用 帮我个忙 剩下的给你
Naw. Do me a favor for the rest.
到那头去告诉Lex 有个女孩想见他
Go up the block and tell Lex there's a girl that want to see him
- 就在Fort后面的操场上 - 女孩?
- at the playground behind Fort. - Girl?
告诉他Patrice要他八点后到操场去
Tell him Patrice say he should come to the playground after 8:00.
你干嘛不自己告诉他
Why don't you tell him yourself?
听着 我可不想听Bodie抱怨我翘班
Look, dog, I don't want to be taking none of Bodie's shit today about cutting work.
好吗 就帮我个忙
All right? Just do me that favor.
Pandemic
Pandemic!
这儿有Pandemic
Pandemic right here!
这么皮包骨的家伙可真会出汗
For a skinny motherfucker, he sure do sweat some.
咱得在车上放件备用的
We got to keep an extra change in the car
这样就不用下午回家了
so we don't have to come home in the middle of the day.
我们现在都迟了很多了 那...
Well, we're way past late now, so...
- 见鬼 - 等等 我来
- Damn it! - Here, let me.
嗨  Norman
Hey, Norman.
也许我回头用一阵夹子才行
Maybe I'll go to clip-on for a while.
- 嗨 Terri有最新的民调数据 - 你的支持率上升了吗
- Hey, Terri got in new polling data. - Did you get a bump?
要全部揭晓她才会告诉我
She won't show me anything till it's all broke down,
不过我的支持率应该有上升 对吧
but, yeah, I deserve a bump, don't l?
还有四周 Jen
Four more weeks, Jen.
与妻子孩子的美妙时光
Quality time with the wife and kids.
多少时间来着 四分钟?
That's what, four minutes?
六分钟
More like six.
Six.
该死 我该云雨一番才对
Shit, I could have got laid.
唷 唷 Chris 我不是...
Yo. Yo, Chris, l-- I didn't--
没什么的
Yeah. It's good.
Pandemic
Pandemic!
这儿有Pandemic
Pandemic right here!
没找到Lex 那个瘦巴巴的丧家犬呢
No Lex. Where's that skinny mope?
早前还在这儿呢
He was here earlier.
该死的 我们会回来的 明早逮住他 没问题的
Well, fuck it. We'll come back. Jack him tomorrow, no problem.
好吧
All right.
汽水也一起喝
Share the sodas, too.
- 你好吗 你好吗 - 嗨
- What's up? What's up? - Hey.
你好
What's up?
我赶紧跟你说句话
Let me holla at you real quick.
什么事
What up?
你照我说的做了?
You did like I said?
- 是的 - 嗯 你应该是的
- Yeah. - Yeah, you must have,
因为那家伙一旦去了
because the nigga went up the block.
就再也回不来了
He ain't never coming back down.
Chris和Snoop...
Chris and Snoop--
嘭
pow!
- 什么 - 瞧
- What? - Look.
好好干 知道不
Just be cool, all right?
英雄们凯旋了
Our heroes back from the wars.
民调票数累计好了
Those poll numbers tallied up yet?
不太差
Not too bad, either.
Royce 35% 你 26% Gray 20%
Royce, 35; you, 26; Gray, 20.
19%尚未决定
19% undecided.
要是比率不再上升  我们就完了 我要的是30%
We're fucked if we haven't moved any more than that. I need to be at 30,
还需要Tony拿到25个百分点
and I need Tony taking 25 of his points.
Royce的反对率上升了
Royce's negatives are way up.
差不多是34%支持票 43%反对
Like what, 34% unfavorable to 43% favorable?
他是受攻击焦点
He's vulnerable.
Geri 你要明白
Geri, understand this.
想赢的话 就得让Tony Gray
In order to win, I need Tony Gray
拿下Royce的很多支持票
to take a huge bite out of Royce's lead-- huge.
Tony才提高了多少
Tony's moved, what?
过去一个月 才两个百分点
Two points in the last month:
这民调率说明五分之一的人还没想好
That poll says one in five voters hasn't decided anything yet.
对啊 首期的广播宣传有奇效了 对吧
Yeah. The first batch of radio spots worked magic, didn't they?
我们多少钱打水漂了啊
How much money we piss away on those?
看看第一区的数据 那可是我的选区
Look at these First District figures. I mean, that's my base,
我才37%支持率 还有24%未定?
and I'm polling 37% with 24% undecided?
操蛋 我完了
Fuck me! I'm done!
Tommy 还没人关注竞选
Tommy, nobody's focused on this race yet.
我们会拿下第一区的
We're gonna own the First.
Chris 看看Royce在第四区的得票
Christ, look at what Royce is polling in the Fourth.
Tony无疑在西巴尔的摩受到了牵制
No doubt, Tony's got to get some traction in West Baltimore.
对 他需要有25%的票率
Yeah, he needs to be rounding 25%
还要往30%靠 顺便说一句
and headed for 30. And, by the way,
谁能告诉我 第六区怎么有64%黑人选民的
who can tell me when the fuck did the Sixth District become 64% black?
五年前最后一次重划区
About five years ago in the last redistricting,
我没记错的话 那是为了 让你在第一区有更多白人选民
mostly as I recall, to give your ass more white votes over there in the First.
我当时他妈的怎么想的
What the fuck was I thinking?
现在到竞选日还有很多变数呢
A hell of a lot can happen between now and election day.
我以前比Royce的民调率高多了 结果还不是输了
I've been ahead further than Royce is and lost.
我赢不了
I can't win this.
Tommy 你上哪儿去
Tommy, where the fuck you going?
我才是你的司机啊
I'm your ride home, man.
这人懂民调
The man can read a poll.
你喝酒了?
You been drinking?
我没事
I'm fine.
你另找个地方没事去
Well, you need to be fine somewhere else.
公园午夜就清场了
Park curfew is midnight.
这城市一天就一宗命案  你却到这儿来
City's averaging a murder a day, and here you are
- 讲什么公园的规定 - 你算老几 自作聪明
- with Rec and Park rules? - What are you, a smart ass?
抱歉 我没什么意思
Sorry. I didn't mean nothing.
我认识你吧
Don't I know you?
我在竞选市长
I'm running for mayor.
Tommy Carcetti 第一区的
Tommy Carcetti, First District.
我大概20分钟后回来 议员
I'll be coming back through in about 20, Councilman.
帮个忙 开车走吧
Do me a favor and take it down the road.
Randy?
来了 太太
Yes, ma'am.